qalo.com 2017-02-05

# QALO - Privacy Policy

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.qalo.com and QALO LLC ("the Company") and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to QALO LLC include www.qaloring.com, QALO and "the company". The company website is an athletic jewelry site. By using the company website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. This privacy policy applies to these sites and other sites, mobile apps or other online services we operate that link to this policy (collectively, referred to below as the site).

**Collection of your Personal  Information**

The Company may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase the companies products and services, we collect billing and credit card information in order to process your online transaction.  We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

**Collection of Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by the company. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the company website in order to improve and customize our services.

 Visitors should also note that non-personal information and data may be automatically collected by the Company through the use of “cookies” or other similar technologies such as web beacons.

 The Company has no control or responsibility for the data collection and use of said data by third parties that process online transactions. If you make a purchase on our site and use a third party payment provider to make payment, certain information is transmitted to the payment provider which is subject to their own privacy policy. The Company encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from the company so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. The company is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Company website. Any third party links we provide are merely for the sake of user convenience.

**Use of your Personal Information**

QALO collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s), for general business purposes and to deliver the services you have requested. 

 The Company may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from the company and its affiliates. The Company may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

 The company does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

 The Company may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. The Company may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to The company, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

 QALO may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within the company, in order to determine what the company services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within the company to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

 QALO will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith or belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on t or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of the company; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the company, or the public.

**Security of your Personal Information**

To secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, QALO uses the following: 

**Shopify**

**Children Under Thirteen**

The Company does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. 

**Disconnecting your QALO Account from Third Party Websites**

You will be able to connect your company account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR Company ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. If you are uncomfortable with your public profiles, such as facebook or twitter, being mentioned in our blog then please let us know prior to posting material in our blog. A blog post, with you involved, would not be put up without your permission in the first place.

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from QALO by contacting us here:

\- Email: support@qalo.com

**Changes to this Statement**

The company will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. The company encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how the company is protecting your information. 

**Contact Information**

The company welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that The company has not adhered to this Statement, please contact the company at: 

QALO LLC 

_________________ 

3011 S Croddy Way 

Santa Ana, CA 92704

(714) 464-3252

Email Address: 

support@qalo.com

Effective as of February 29, 2016
